[{"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You look like... my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "'Bout written you off. How long have you been in town", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Four months", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "In the Field Museum once", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It worked when you were in sixth grade", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah. Big fan", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Uh, I think there's been a mistake. I didn't save that woman", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Every little boy's fantasy", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I have a job", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What's wrong, my friend?  C'mon, you only beat up the roof when something's on your mind.  How's my friend doing", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I know he's out, but how's he doing", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Had to take on another fire bar", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He didn't listen? He was a fucking candidate! He was your responsibility. He shouldn't have been there in the first place, my friend.  You burned him", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You told my friend about our arson lead. It's all over the fucking news", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "-- Bullshit! You knew what I told you wasn't ready for the papers", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "-- You could have scared the son of a bitch off. We may never bust him now. All for a couple's political points", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Yeah? And just how much of all this has been", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "...He wasn't listening to the right thing..", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You don't know... nobody knows..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "-- No no, your turn. Tell me a story", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Sure you do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah, it's just another memory in my life right now. And I got way too many of them..", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah? What have you got to do?  Look at you. Look at your face. All the things you must be thinking. Man, you must really hate my guts. Well, you know what? It's okay", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I saw it", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "When dad died, I saw another fire..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I saw my friend's back! I saw the burn! I put it there! my friend, my friend, he's been killing people", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "How do you know", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I knew when you came looking for the chemicals. Looking for me", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "They were for the fucking boat, my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I quit two days ago, my friend", "docId": "Backdraft.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I don't have the slightest idea..", "qsentId": 32}]